adulttvlive.net 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy | AdultTVLive.net

At AdultTVLive.net, accessible from http://www.adulttvlive.net, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by AdultTVLive.net and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at adulttvlive.net@domainsbyproxy.com

## Log Files

AdultTVLive.net follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, AdultTVLive.net uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

## Our Advertising Partners

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

## Privacy Policies of Advertising Partners

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of AdultTVLive.net.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on AdultTVLive.net, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that AdultTVLive.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

## Third Party Privacy Policies

AdultTVLive.net’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?

## Are minors welcome?

The Website is not intended for minors. You will only access the Website if you are at least  
18-years old and have reached the age of majority where you live. AdultTVLive prohibits all persons who do  
not meet the age requirements from accessing the Website. Minors must not access the Website or use  
its services.  
AdultTVLive does not knowingly collect any informa1on about children, minors, or anyone under 18-years  
old. If you are under 18-years old, AdultTVLive asks that you do not access to AdultTVLive.

## WARNING: 18+ Content

AdultTVLive.net is based on 18+ content or website for adult person/above 18+ age. So it’s strictly forbidden for under age or below 18+ age. The TV Channel you are about to view contain content of an adult nature. This TV Channel is designed for ADULTS only and may include pictures, videos and materials that some viewers may find offensive. If you are under the age of 18, if such material offends you or if it is illegal to view such material in your community or country please do not access the website and also left the website immediately. The following terms and conditions apply to this TV Channel. Entering this page via the link below will constitute your agreement to the following terms and conditions:  
I am 18 years of age or older.  
I accept all resposibility for my own actions.  
I agree that I am legally bound to these Terms and Conditions  
It is not our intention to offend, so if you are under 18 years of age, or feel that you may be offended by this TV Channel, please go elsewhere

## Content

We DO NOT host any broadcasts on this website/server. All streams on our website are found freely available around the Internet. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated neither claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of broadcasts/streams played on our site.  
Whereas we do not filter such references, we cannot and don’t attempt to control, censor, or block any material that may be considered offensive, defamatory, libelous, obnoxious, inaccurate, deceptive, unlawful or otherwise distressing neither do we accept responsibility for such content or the consequences of such content being made available.  
Material may be inappropriately described or subject to restrictions such as copyright, licensing and other limitations, and it is the responsibility of those having access to such material to comply with any and all lawful obligations arising from such material coming into their possession and thus mitigate any alleged transgression.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in AdultTVLive.net. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
